Hey, welcome back. Before we move on and start to actually write some game code, there's
嘿，欢迎回来。在我们继续并开始实际编写一些游戏代码之前，有一件事我想提一下。
one thing that I'd like to mention, and that is the object pointer. Later when we dive
我想提到一件事，那就是对象指针。以后当我们深入到
into the engine's source code, instead of the traditional way of using a pointer as
的源码时，不是用指针作为成员变量的传统方式。
a member variable, this is something that we'll see inside of the header file. And
一个成员变量，而是在头文件中看到的东西。而
that is the t-object pointer. It is created in Unreal Engine 5. It's meant to replace
这就是t-object指针。它是在虚幻引擎5中创建的。它的目的是为了取代
the traditional way of creating a pointer as member variable. Comparing to a raw pointer,
传统的将指针创建为成员变量的方式。与一个原始的指针相比、
it has more features. So it supports access tracking and lazy loading. So what access
它有更多的功能。所以它支持访问跟踪和懒惰加载。因此，访问
tracking means is it can allow us to track when exactly an object has been accessed.
跟踪的意思是它可以让我们跟踪一个对象到底是什么时候被访问的。
And this can be quite useful for debugging purposes since it can help us to quickly identify
这对于调试来说是非常有用的，因为它可以帮助我们快速确定
when and where an object is being accessed in the code. And as for lazy loading, it could
在代码中何时何地访问一个对象。而对于懒惰加载，它可以
allow us to load an object into memory only when it's needed. So potentially this could
允许我们只在需要的时候将一个对象加载到内存中。因此，这可能会
help us to reduce the amount of time of loading access inside of our editor. But one thing
帮助我们减少在编辑器中加载访问的时间。但是有一件事
to look out for is using the object pointer as member variable has no impact on performance.
要注意的是，使用对象指针作为成员变量，对性能没有影响。
So it won't magically make our game run faster as it just contains more features than raw
所以它不会神奇地使我们的游戏运行得更快，因为它只是包含了比原始指针更多的功能。
pointers. Another thing to mention is the object pointer is only designed to use as
指针。另一件要提到的事情是，对象指针只被设计为作为
a member variable. So if you use it for a local variable inside of our function or an
一个成员变量。因此，如果你在我们的函数中使用它作为一个局部变量或者一个
input parameter, they will be converted into a raw pointer automatically. And same thing
输入参数，它们将被自动转换为原始指针。而同样的事情
goes for a shipping build. So this is only something that we can use inside of our editor
也是如此。所以这只是我们可以在编辑器中使用的东西
and it could potentially offer us better developing experience. Whether or not to use it is completely
而且它有可能为我们提供更好的开发体验。是否使用它完全是
optional in 5.1. As of now, there are still plenty of raw pointers inside of Unreal's
在5.1中是可选的。到目前为止，在虚幻的5.1版本中仍然有很多原始的指针。
source code. And since we have no need of the features it provides and the code template
源代码。因为我们不需要它所提供的功能，而且我们使用的代码模板仍然使用原始指针作为成员变量。
we use still uses the raw pointer as member variable, I'm gonna stick with the old traditional
我们使用的代码模板仍然使用原始指针作为成员变量，我将坚持使用传统的
way of declaring pointers as member variable. And later when we see syntax like this in
的方式将指针声明为成员变量。而以后当我们看到在
Unreal's source code, you just need to know this is just a pointer. Alright, with this
虚幻的源代码时，你只需要知道这只是一个指针。好了，有了这个
out of the way, starting from next lecture, we can actually write the game code we need.
了，从下一节课开始，我们可以真正地编写我们需要的游戏代码了。
I'll see you in the next lecture.
我们将在下一讲中再见。
[Music]
[音乐]